[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 12, "question": "Plus, do you believe him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 13, "answer": "What I went through was real.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers", "NRA"]}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "WP", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "What do you do to change their minds and therefore the chances of success of this attempt to change the law?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Well, Piers, what you have to understand, after these horrific shootings that we go through, what the NRA does is already start to put out all the negative stuff, and then the members, to be very honest with you, start getting nervous about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["McCarthy"]}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "How many more types do people need?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "RBR", "NNS", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "Well, Piers, I have to tell you, and Representative McCarthy, thank you so much for your leadership.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "How do you respond to that particular argument, which is they believe under their Second Amendment right, they should be allowed an AR-15?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "I will tell you, if you talk to professionals, hunters and certainly sportsmen, they'll tell you that's probably not the kind of gun to use.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "Let me -- let me ask just very, very quickly, Michael Nutter, do you believe that you can win this argument and get an assault weapons ban reinstated?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "Yes, I believe in the American public.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Nutter"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "Do you think that that could have played any part in causing him to suddenly go off like this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "We have no idea.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Albuquerque"]}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "Did you have any information about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "This is a semirural area outside of Albuquerque.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "How many -- how many people of the three million who own AR-15s, military-style assault rifles in this country have ever used them to defend themselves?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "CD", "CD", "WP", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "I can't get you a number, but I'll be glad -- I'll be glad to try to find a number.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "I haven't heard of any, so the answer comes back at you, why does anybody need, in civilian life, a weapon that belongs in a military battlefield, as General Stanley McChrystal and General Colin Powell both said?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "First of all, the civilian AR-15 is not an automatic weapon.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["General Stanley McChrystal"], "PERSON": ["Colin Powell"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "Why are automatic weapons banned in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Because they were felt to be too dangerous.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "Why are they too dangerous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "Because of high-volume of fire, which you don't get from a semiautomatic weapon.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Do you know how many bullets the shooter at Aurora, James Holmes, fired per minute with his AR-15?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "-NONE-", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["James Holmes"], "LOCATION": ["Aurora"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "How many more bullets do you need to fire, Mr. Speaker, before that qualifies as a dangerous killing machine by your criteria?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "RBR", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "Well, by my criteria, and this goes back to the question of what you respect, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Speaker"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "What else do you call them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "This is lovely propaganda.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "What else do you call it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "I would simply say to you that millions of people by your own definition own an AR-15.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "Do you know how many different types of guns she has permitted to remain in legal circulation in America under any proposal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "No, like this.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ":", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "So this is what this year the government is willing to permit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "Why -- why would she permit twice as many.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "What is the difference?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "Wait a second.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 315, "question": "Where are you on the pistols that killed most of the people in Chicago, Piers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "My position --", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Chicago"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "It's OK if we kill them individually?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "Are you saying three, four, five, and that's OK?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "CD", ",", "CD", ",", "CD", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "Let my position very, very clear.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 331, "question": "So why don't you share your real view?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Many of the other proposals --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "Wouldn't you ban pistols if you could?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "Let me -- let me explain what I would do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "The semiautomatics that can fire 100 bullets in a minute are not dangerous and they should be lawful?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "I think the founding fathers would have found this entire debate strange because they actually believed in individual freedom and they were very suspicious of big government, and they would find the idea that you're going to permit, to use the word you kept using.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "But you do agree with not permitting Americans to have automatic weapons?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "I think 50-caliber machine guns would be bizarre.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", ":", "DT", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "Would that young man -- would that young man -- would that young men, have slaughtered five of his family if he hadn't had access to the firearms in the house?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "MD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ":", "MD", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "To -- no, but now you're back to a different question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Newt"]}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "You want to put -- so you're saying you want the state to step in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "But, Newt, my final point is he clearly didn't protect them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "It's a tragedy, we don't know all of the answers, but, you know, this is a situation where we want less Americans to be killed by guns, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "I like your answer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "Why do you need these mass killing machines?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "Here is the thing, Piers, is the fact this is the most popular rifle in the United States.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "Do you ladies agree with automatic weapons being banned?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "That's not the issue at hand right now, because they are banned.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 469, "question": "Do you believe automatic weapons should be banned, as they are?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "Basically, that is something that I don't really --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "Do you agree with the government's decision, which is an on-going law, to ban automatic weapons?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "Right now, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "Can you explain that to me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "Both know that the basic difference is you pull the trigger and it shoots, as opposed to the automatic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "Do you know one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "For example, yes, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "Do you believe that women should be allowed on the front line in combat in the military?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "I believe -- I believe they should.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "Am I basically not wise enough to America to understand why it's apparently not an infringement on the Second Amendment to ban automatic weapons, but it is to ban an AR-15 that can fire 100 bullets in a minute?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "To answer the first question, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "It's not just me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "It's not just you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "Where is that body having the same kind of political and financial muscle?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "There are some good organizations.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "When you see 2,200 guns can remain even with the proposal she's got, this apparently isn't dinged deemed enough to defend yourselves?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "DT", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "There's never enough.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "Quick question on Hillary Clinton, how do you think she fared after the Benghazi hearings?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "I thought she faired brilliantly.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hillary Clinton"], "LOCATION": ["Benghazi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Do you sit easily with the mantle of legend?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "No, because I don't feel like one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "Here is the question I never thought I would ask John Elway, have you ever had a fake girlfriend?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Elway"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 641, "question": "Do you buy it all, from what you've seen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 642, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "So the question I guess for you now, since you are in this great high-powered position with the broncos, are you actively encouraging the Broncos now to have fake girlfriends in the hopes it boosts their play?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "No, no, I'm not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 653, "question": "How good of a player is he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 654, "answer": "He's a good player, a good football player.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "But as somebody who has grown up in American culture and presumably around guns, when you were a youngster, what is your view of the debate as it stands?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "You know, I'm still kind of waiting to hear both sides of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 666, "question": "As someone who hunts, shoots, so on, for sport, do you see any need for a civilian to have one of these military style rifles that can pump out 100 bullets a minute?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "WP", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "RP", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 667, "answer": "No, that's one area.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "But do you see why anybody would need one as a civilian?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "NN", "MD", "VB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "I do not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 677, "question": "What mistakes did they make, the Republicans, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNPS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 678, "answer": "I don't know if you can define them as mistakes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 683, "question": "Where is your money going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 684, "answer": "I can't bet, so my money isn't going anywhere.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 688, "question": "Ravens and 49ers, who is going to take it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 689, "answer": "Two good football teams.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Dove Men Plus Care"]}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 692, "question": "Tell me briefly about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 693, "answer": "It's Dove Men Plus Care.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 697, "question": "Are you comfortable in your own skin, John?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 698, "answer": "I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["John?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 701, "question": "How have you come to terms with not being able to be out there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "That takes a while.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]